hoursinfo.com 2016-06-18

# Privacy Policy - Hours Info

www.hoursinfo.com (the Website) collects and manages user data according to the following Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collected**

The Website servers collect the following non-personal identification information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; web pages requested; referring web page; browser used; browser language; date and time; and statistics identifying particular IP addresses from which The Website is accessed.

**Use of Collected Information**

The Website uses browser-IP-address information and anonymous-browser history (cookies) to report information about site accesses and for profiling purposes. The information is used to improve Web presentation and utilization.

**Distribution of Collected Information**

These aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Website and service. We currently use Google Analytics (traffic analysis, SEO optimization). Feel free to check out Google’s own Privacy Policies to find out more.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

Should you have any question or concern, please write to contact@hourscenter.com.
